

ABOUT ME

Brazilian and 23 years old. Electrical engineer and student of the 8th period of economic sciences. Interested in topics related to electronics, finance, data analysis and artificial intelligence. In my free time, I like to play basketball, play computer games, develop electronic projects or watch NBA games.

CONTACT

Cellphone: +55 (44) 99945-8861. E-mail: joaovmarcotti@hotmail.com. Location: Maringá, PR, Brazil.

LANGUAGES

- English Advanced.
- German Beginner.

COURSES

- Excel: basic to advanced.
- Hardware programming in MicroPython.
- Introduction to Python
- Python for data science and analytics.
- Python for finance: investments and data analysis.

SKILLS

- Exploratory analysis.
- Machine learning.
- MicroPython.
- Microsoft Excel.
- Power BI
- Python.
- SQL.

PORTFOLIO

https://github.com/joaopaivaa/Data Science Portfolio

JOÃO PAIVA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Finance Intern

LIT Portas em ACM. June 2021 - July 2021.

- Cash flow control.
- Assistance in corporate separation.
- Elaboration of spreadsheet for budgets of doors.

Inverters Lab Intern

THA Soluções. July 2022 - November 2022.

- Fault diagnosis and repair of photovoltaic inverters.
- Elaboration of laboratory control sheets.

M&A Intern

Stonecapital. February 2023 - June 2023.

- Market analysis.
- Valuation by analysis of multiples.
- · Analysis of financial statements.
- Customer prospecting (sell-side).

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Universidade Estadual de Maringá - UEM

Electrical Engineering Bachelor Degree. January 2018 - June 2023.

UniCesumar

Economics Bachelor Degree. March 2020 - December 2023.

Fundação Getúlio Vargas - FGV

Executive MBA in Business Analytics and Big Data. July 2023 - Setember 2024.

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

- Development of an electromyography sensor. April 2019 - April 2021.
- Member of the Lapidando Jóias UEM project. August 2019 - December 2019.
- Financial Director of Team Capibaja UEM. June 2020 - August 2022.
- Development of a thermocirculator applied to the Sous Vide culinary technique. March 2021 - April 2023.
- Development of an algorithm to rebalance the Ibovespa through Markowitz's Modern Portfolio Theory.
 May 2022 - February 2023.